LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
Togusa!
Please!
He is an extremely unstable condition right now.
Major...
Please take a look at my memory.
It was the Ministry of Health,
Labour and Welfare, after all.
I didn't get shot in the head.
Intubate!
Okay!
While he undergoes surgery, extract the last
sixteen hours of memories from his cyberbrain.
That's impossible!
Please do it.
We must have that information at all costs.
Traces
Left
Behind
How is it?
It must be a side-effect of anesthetics.
There is too much noise.
The input will even include
his emotional ups and downs,
so our perceptions may be
influenced by them as well.
It doesn't matter.
Let's do it.
His heartbeat is abnormally high.
That idiot... Of course he's going to
get downed if he's feeling this heroic!
Let's summarize the situation.
Togusa deduced that the hackers at the
vocational aid centre were after paper media?
and he subsequently made frequent visits to the Ministry of
Health, Labour and Welfare in order to confirm his suspicions.
In the process, he found that a list was
missing from a vast collection of documents.
And that was the list of Murai
vaccine recipients, correct?
Correct.
It's unclear, but it seems that Togusa visited
the Sunflower Society, which needed the list,
and became caught up in an assault there.
It is clear!
It was Narcotics who gunned Togusa down!
This means that the assault team,
which specialises in vicious crimes,
is going around massacring civilians!
Their intent was to seize the file by force
or to eradicate it from existence, perhaps?
The fact that Imakurusu's name was on the
list led to the present circumstances.
That is what it seems like to me, at least.
Who cares about the hows and whys?!!!
We'll find out what they were as soon
as we get those Narcotics bastards!!!
Don't get so worked up over these memories.
The media should be broadcasting
falsified information already.
The truth has been erased.
Major, who is this Imakurusu person?
Imakurusu Hisahi, the former Chairman of
the Central Drug Evaluation Committee.
An authority on cyberbrain sclerosis, as well as
the chairman of the Medical Association in Japan
Even though he has retired from his
post on the evaluation committee,
he is thought to have maintained
strong connections with the Ministry.
All right, Major, go to Imakurusu.
I will investigate how the Narcotic's
assault team came to intervene.
Understood.
Pazu and Saitou,
come with me to Imakurusu's residence.
Batou, you will continue to analyse
Togusa's memory with Ishikawa and Bomer.
You're joking!
I should be investigating Narcotics!
And what do you intend to do
after going there in such a mood?
I'll call you if need to.
What mood do I need to be in, then?!!!
She means to say that you need to cool off a bit.
You're saying that we should
feel fine after seeing that?!
Right now, you're affected by Togusa's memories.
Her decision is sound.
Excuse me.
And just who may you be?
I'm Aramaki from Public Safety Section 9.
I heard that orders for the sweep of the
Sunflower Society, which was conducted last night,
bypassed the chief of Narcotics
and came directly from you.
I would like to hear your reasons for it.
How rude!
It's fine.
I'm about to meet with the press.
Members of the Sunflower Society are a sly lot.
In order to proceed with due caution, only the members
of the assault team were to be aware of the operation.
Unfortunately, the members of the Sunflower Society
indicated that they were prepared to resist at all cost,
so we were forced to use extreme measures.
They even set fire to the building.
Chief, it's time.
It seems that we do not have to intervene, then.
However, there is one thing
I am still concerned about.
I believe that it must be due to some coincidence,
but one of our own happened
to be at the scene last night.
Now then, we shall meet again someday.
Is that all right, sir?
Let him be.
If he took the trouble of coming here,
then it means that he has nothing.
Gayle!
It's of no use.
It seems that he has already left the premises.
Public Safety's on to us!
We don't have much time!
Public Safety?
Section 9!
Get to Imakurusu before they do!
Ah yes, that group of soldiers-turned-cyborgs?
In that case, I may need "that".
The thing I have been requesting.
All right.
I'll make the necessary arrangements for it.
However, do not leave any evidence if
you come in contact with Section 9.
Understood.
Without a trace.
Will you betray me now that we've come to this?
IMAKURUSU
It's pretty bad.
The starting signal, I see.
Chief, we were late.
It appears that there were
visitors who came before us.
It must have been the assault team.
However, judging from the circumstances,
Imakurusu appears to have fled in advance.
Probably.
If so, then there is a high possibility
that he will use some sort of communication.
I see.
Perhaps we should ask a favour
of the American Empire's NRO?
You mean the global satellite
communications interception network?
Yep.
Chief?
Permission granted.
I will have the Ministry of Foreign
Affairs grant permission ex post facto.
I have enough favours piled up with the CIA.
Understood.
It's time for Big Brother to make an appearance.
We can now tap all communications
in Japan in real time.
Here it comes!
God, not only is the amount of data
enough to crash the terminals within
this building, but it's enough to crash
those within a one kilometre radius
Maybe we'll ask for backup from the old geezers.
Damn it, this is the end.
I shouldn't have run.
It was you who stole the file!
Now, I wouldn't be surprised if they
thought I was the one who betrayed them.
You wouldn't have become serious if I
hadn't taken these measures, would you?
They are not as lenient as
you would like to believe.
I feel sorry for the Sunflower Society's members.
However, I have already decided
that I will not give up until I have
exposed what went on behind the
advancement of micromachine treatments.
You are a naive one, aren't you?
If we had approved the vaccine at the
time, it would have been quite possible
that the achievements of cyberbrain
technology would have been rejected,
despite the technology’s ongoing
application in various fields and continuing
development, and that we would have
suffered regression as a result.
However, no law condones the
suppression of valid research results.
You misunderstand!
I did not blindly object to the vaccine.
I was prepared to approve it on the
condition that sufficient data was collected.
Then, what was the basis upon which SERANO
Genomix's utility design was approved
within a mere three months,
despite the fact that SERANO
Genomix was a latecomer in
micromachine research at the time?
That was all according to a
predetermined trajectory that was
paved at the Ministry of Health,
Labour and Welfare's initiative!
We on the Committee were just made to look like fools.
A convenient excuse.
Similarly, the Micromachine
Industries company that you directed
had its design approved within one month.
And in return, you people raked in
annual profits of one trillion yen
from protein particles that had no
effect against cyberbrain sclerosis!
It was obviously a fraud committed
under the government's direction!
The poor ignorant patients who believed in the
treatment and died after paying high medical fees...
Just how do you intend to make excuses for them?
Micromachine have now been shown to
be effective to a certain degree!
You cannot definitely say that it ended in catastrophe
so far as the treatment of sclerosis went.
If so, then why do you not treat your
own condition with micromachines?
You were the only person who was in a position
capable of preventing this lamentable situation.
You chose a career to save lives;
why did you not decide to do so?
I had prided myself on being committed to a life
dedicated to the treatment of cyberbrain sclerosis!
But Murai-
Beat you to your goal.
Was it envy?
I heard that you even went through
the trouble of having a "not
approved" seal specially made
to destroy the Murai vaccine.
Now, they gloat on their thrones after
taking advantage of your damned petty pride.
If you know that much,
what is it that you want me to do?!
You're quite capable of invading my
cyberbrain and taking over, ghost and all!
There is no point in that.
Now that your life is being
maintained by that vaccine,
please disclose the truth of your own free will.
Whether you spend the rest
of your days as a good man
or be pointed out as a heartless
criminal after your death,
the choice is yours.
Laughing Man... just who are you?
Why did you, who displays such blatant heroism,
commit such acts of corporate terrorism
and obtain a massive amount of money?
I have never said that I was the Laughing Man.
Besides, there is another who used
corporate terrorism to steal money.
It can't be...!
It is as you realised.
Listen to me.
If we are to bring them to justice,
we need another playing
card besides your testimony.
Until I return, please do not leave
this room under any circumstances.
Do you understand?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Um, did you need anything, sir?
No, not anymore.
Please go.
Excuse me, then.
Oh, actually...
Is there a public terminal somewhere near here?
He should be fine.
His blood pressure is stable as well.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
However, if he experiences some sort
of physical disability or aftereffects,
he may just have to resign himself
to getting some cybernetic implants.
I'm sorry about the foul weather.
Well, it can't be helped.
Today was the only day that worked for us, anyway.
It's me, Imakurusu. Help me!
Please clear Niimi's doubts about me!
Yes, at that golf course I told you about.
I'm counting on you!
Big Brother's great!
We don't know for sure yet.
All it means is that our voice
pattern filter caught "Imakurusu".
Correlating voice pattern of caller
with that of Imakurusu Hisahi.
Correlation with Imakurusu Hisashi's
voice pattern is 36% complete.
Determining location of terminal
used by caller, starting search.
Proceeding to determine location of
terminal, starting search.
Determined signal origin.
Proceeding to trace signal path.
Hey, the operators are crashing in droves!
Proceeding to activate trace program
via communication satellites.
We have backups.
Hey, we're lucky today!
We're getting hits all over the place!
That's to pay you for borrowing your cyberbrains.
You're a crook.
After all, even if they're old, if you hook them up
in parallel, you can get a lot of power out of them.
How is it?
We have just determined the location
where Imakurusu used the terminal.
Now, we will confirm whether it was him.
Chief, a direct call.
What?
This is Niimi.
Is that true?!
Yes.
No, I will take care of it immediately!
Is that you, Gayle? It's me.
We have Imakurusu's location!
He's at Kouhoku Country Club!
Get over there!
The idiot...
He chose the wrong one to run to.
He is at Kouhoku Country Club.
His presence was confirmed two minutes ago at the terminal
that is located on the northern pedestrian walkway.
It's a match!
However, what concerns me is who he called-
Who cares as long as we know where he is?!!!
Old man, we'll be faster than the Major.
I'm going out in the chopper!
All right, get him before anyone else does.
Ishikawa!
Are you able to trace Imakurusu?!!!
After that, he went into room 909 in an annex.
He is stationary at the moment.
Bomer, what do you think about this?
This guy.
A protected phone number that was assigned the highest
priority in the American Empire's surveillance list?
You are attempting to access a confidential government line.
Please enter your password.
Yes. Officially, the number doesn't exist.
But isn't this the number for
the ruling party's headquarters?
How is it, squad leader?
How's the MSDF's 303 model?
The Marine has a pretty artistic
form with its fluid lines.
Now, if those Section 9 people show
up, we can get actual combat data.
Squad leader we have confirmed a chopper
that's heading towards the target.
It appears to be Section 9.
Oh yeah? What good timing!
All right, you guys try to secure Imakurusu first.
This one requires time for system start up.
After you guys cut off the escape
route, leave the rest to me!
They're...
You are Imakurusu Hisahi, correct?
I'm the police.
An Assault Team is coming.
Let's get you out of here!
Don't come near me!
Batou, are you all right?
Yeah, barely,
but we're hemmed in.
Can you evacuate using the chopper?
Negative. Not while Imakurusu is with me.
Hang on!
I'm almost there!
Even if they are invisible, it doesn't mean
that their very existence is invisible as well.
How are they going to advance?!
Is that you, Major?!
I have secured an escape route.
Let's return to the lobby for now.
Go!
Down!!!
What was that?
An Armour Suit?!
Batou, I will distract it.
Don't be an idiot! That's my role!
It's not that I don't have confidence in you,
but that thing cannot be stopped.
This is a direct order!
Take Imakurusu and evacuate the premises!
Damn it...
Don't get done in by that thing, either!
Major, we'll be there shortly!
Not even a direct hit can pierce its armour?
Saitou! Hand that thing over!!!
H-hey, open the hatch!
Please don't!
I-I can't breathe!
More this way!
That's right!
Put him on the chopper and be quick about it.
All right...
The idiot... Wait here.
Hey, you two! Don't move!
All right, don't move, okay?
Imakurusu!
Imakurusu was hit!
Call for an ambulance!
Laughing Man... is that who you are?
What...?
Did you say "Laughing Man"?
What is going on?
LIST OF MURAI VACCINE RECIPIENTS
This file is...!
Thermo-optical camouflage?!
No, that's not it!
You bastard... you stole my eyes, didn't you?!
Where are you?! Are you still nearby?!
Where are you?!!!
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up